entrancecorner.com 2009-05-21

# Entrance corner-Privacy policy

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Web pages created or maintained by Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

We will not release, sell, rent, or trade the personal information of any of our customers to any third party. We respect and understand the importance of privacy and security for our customers. Any personal information collected by Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd, including contact information, unique identifier information, transactional and financial information, will be kept private. Upon request, all Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd. Customers can access and verify their information.

In case such a need arises in the future it will be done with full disclosure of how and what data shall be shared. All data collected on the websites owned/maintained by Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd. is treated with the utmost care and respect for individual right to privacy. We at Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd. are committed towards creating a transparent and consumer friendly ecosystem of conducting business.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers or e-mail addresses on-line may receive telephone calls or emails from us for relevant information regarding entrance examination related services. 

If at any point you no longer wish to receive information from EntranceCorner, you can e-mail us at info@entrancecorner.com and we will remove you from our contact lists.

This privacy policy is intended to be a generic guideline while using the services extended EntranceCorner. It extends to our website www.entrancecorner.com.

Step Into Web Software Pvt. Ltd. reserves the right to change certain aspects of this policy as and when it deems fit. The users may be notified of such changes and can be given an option to opt-out if they disagree with the revised policies.
